Shekh Mohammad Shakawat Hossain

Address

House: 3, Road: 9, Sector: 10 Uttara Model Town, Dhaka-1230

Contact: 01785224746 shakawatnsu@yahoo.com

Linkedin Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shakawat-hossain-43982a7b/

Career Objective

To build long-term career in service industry where I will be able to utilize my skills, experience and education to obtain business objective, ensuring interests of all the stakeholders linked with me and confirm my success at any challenge. I am looking for obtaining Managerial position within 3 years by performing and conquering all obstacles and challenges.

Work Experience

Operation Executive- Team Leader (1st July 2018- 31st October 2019) Digital Channel, Genex Infosys Ltd.

Roles:

- ➤ Team development in order to achieve organization goal and clients' business objective.
- > Managing customer service through Social Media LOB of Grameenphone Ltd. includes-
 - GP verified Facebook Fan page
 - ❖ Bioscope verified Facebook Fan page and Email support
 - GP Music verified Fan page
 - ❖ Wowbox verified Fan page
- ➤ Beside above LOB, cooperate other Digital Channel LOB includes:
 - ❖ GP Email service
 - ❖ GP Live Chat service
 - ❖ Skitto Helpline
- Mentoring and guiding agents to provide correct solution of customers' queries & complaints and ensuring best quality service.
- Preparing and maintaining roster for agents.
- > Providing refreshment and performance enhancement coaching to existing agents.
- Coordinate training team to train new joiners during induction period and Quality team to improve service quality.
- Coordinate HR task by taking interviews of agents and maintain updates of Digital Channel team members.
- > Maintaining client relationship by ensuring clients business purpose.

Sr. Trainee (13th July 2016 to 28th June 2018) Digital Channel, Grameenphone Roles:

- Resolving customers' queries and complaints through Email, Live Chat & Social Media.
- Liaison between corporate customers and Key Account Managers.
- Generating sales through Digital Media to valued customers.



- Assisting product development teams to recognize customers' expectations and finding out potential customers.
- Assisting Managers and Team Leaders to mentor new trainees.
- ➤ Assisting MyGP app developer teams to develop new customer friendly features.

Intern, South East Bank Ltd (13th September 2015 – 13th December 2015) Roles:

- Assisting Foreign Exchange Department, Credit & Risk Department & General Banking Department to conduct daily activities.
- ➤ Analysis of loan seekers information and assisting credit risk executives to take final decision.

Professional Degree:

Pursuing CIPS-UK, DIPLOMA IN PROCUREMENT AND SUPPLY (Level 4) from Advance SCS.

Duration: 5th February 2020- Current

ACHIEVEMNTS

- ➤ Second round of Ad Makers Bangladesh 2012 arranged by Young Entrepreneurs Society club of NSU.
- ➤ Participant of Socio Camp 2013 arranged by Social Service Club of NSU.
- ➤ One of the top 35 participants out of 1000 candidates of Fresh Presents Shadhin commentator HUNT- Powered By GTV.

Computer Proficiency

- Proficient in Microsoft Office tools (Powerpoint, Excel, Outlook, Word).
- Proficient in ERP tools (CBIO, CIM, CRM, Skydive, Revechat).

Training

➤ Internal Audit Including General Conception of ISO 9001:2015

Institute: BDjobs Training, Karwan Bazar Training Duration: 1/12/2017 – 2/12/2017

Completed online course training from Alison Course Material on Supply Chain Management.

Personal Traits

- Desperate to achieve
- Passionate for success
- Positive towards challenges
- Communication excellence

- Ready to visit anywhere
- Flexible to adjust in different environment

Education

Masters of Business Administration

Major at Human Resource Management (2017 – 2018)

Current CGPA: 3.19 out of scale 4

North South University

Bachelor in Business Administration

Major: Marketing & Finance (2011 – 2016)

CGPA of BBA: 3.06 out of scale 4

North South University

Higher Secondary Certificate

Rajuk Uttara Model College, Dhaka (2008 - 2010)

Group: Business Studies

GPA: 4.90

Secondary School Certificate

South Point School & College, CTG (2005 - 2008)

Group: Science GPA: 4.63

Personal Information

Name: Shekh Mohammad Shakawat Hossain

Parents: S.M. Amir Hossain & Chamon Ara Hossain

D.O.B: 10th August 1993

Permanent Address: Village: Mirapara, PO: West Gujra, PS: Raujan, District: CTG

NID: 8694343529

References

Mehdi Hasan Zulfiqar

Head of Customer Service

ShopUp Ltd.

Contact: +8801912818717 Email: munich09@gmail.com Relationship: Former Manager

MD. Atique-Ul Islam

Lead Manager

Digital Channels & Distribution, Digital

Grameenphone Ltd.

Contact: +8801711506643

Email: atiqueul.islam@grameenphone.com
Relationship: Former Reporting Supervisor